Guide to the Francis Marion Ownbey Papers 1934-1974
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 3: University Faculty and Teaching Materials
  - Botany 541, Evolution. Course notes, 1968-1973; 300 items. (Box 31, Folder 265-76)
  - Evolutionary Mechanisms, Seminar Papers, 1973; 6 items. (Box 32, Folder 277-82)
  - Entomology/Zoology 511, Principles of Systematic Biology. Syllabus and Notes, 1972; 3 items. (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - Cytogenetics. Notes, 1950-1954; 50 items. (Box 32, Folder 284)
  - Graduate Student Recruitment; Financial Aid, 1955-1970; 100 items. (Box 32, Folder 285)
  - Field Trip, 1941; 3 items. (Box 32, Folder 286)
  - Botany Department Staff, memoranda and minutes, 1967-1974; 150 items. (Box 32, Folder 287)
  - Botany Facilities: Buildings, Greenhouse, Arboretum, 1962-1972; 125 items. (Box 33, Folder 288)
  - Field Area (Smoot Hill) Memoranda and Minutes of Planning Committee, 1967-1971; 125 items. (Box 33, Folder 289)
  - Library Matters, 1951-1969; 150 items. (Box 33, Folder 290)
  - Search Committee for Botany Department Chairman, Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes, 1958-1969; 200 items. (Box 34, Folder 291-292)
  - Grant Funding, 1969-1973; 6 items. (Box 34, Folder 293)
  - National Science Foundation. Research Proposals
    - 1958-1974, 75 items. (Box 34, Folder 294-295)
    - 1958-1974, 75 items. (Box 35, Folder 296-297)
  - Addenda: Drafts of Vascular Plants of the Pacific Northwest Vol. II., by A. Cronquist and C. L. Hitchcock
    - Salicaceae (Box 36)
    - Polygonaceae (Box 36)
    - Chenopodiaceae (Box 36)
    - Amaranthaceae (Box 36)
    - Portulacaceae (Box 36)
    - Caryophyllaceae (Box 36)
    - Ranunculaceae (Box 36)
  - Misc. correspondence (Box 36)